《迷失》前情回顾
previously on lost
怎么会有炸药
Dude, where did that come from?
Locke  要是他想让我们自相残杀呢
Locke! What if he's trying to get we kill each other?
我不会坐以待毙
I ain't just stand here and do nothing!
你要相信我
You just have to trust me.
对不起  医生  我不信
Sorry, doc, I don't.
Sayid
Sayid!
-快走  我会救她  -不  我们一起救她
- Go! I'll get her free.  - No, we can do this!
快走  救Sawyer
Just go! Save Sawyer!
我不会丢下你
I won't leave you.
-我爱你  Sun  -我爱你
- I love you, Sun.  - I love you!
Jin和Sun呢
What about Jin and Sun?
早
Morning.
我做了早餐
I made breakfast.
准确地说  开一盒麦片
You know, technically, opening a box of cereal
不算是做早餐
Is not making breakfast.
你今晚会去音乐会吗
So you're coming to the concert tonight, right?
当然
Absolutely.
你妈也去吗
Is your mom coming, too?
去
Yeah.
怎么了
Why?
你们不会觉得尴尬吧
You're not gonna get all weird, are you?
-我怎么会尴尬  -那就不要
- Why would I get weird?  - Just don't get weird.
我不会的
I won't.
早
Morning.
-早  -早
- Morning.  - Morning.
吃麦片吗
You want some cereal?
好  谢谢
Um, sure. Thanks.
感觉还好吗
How you feeling?
很好
Uh, pretty good.
只是他晚上踢得厉害
I mean, he kicks like crazy at night, so...
我是Jack Shephard
Jack Shephard.
你好  Shephard先生
Hello, Mr. Shephard.
我是大洋航空的
Uh, this is Oceanic Airlines calling
想通知您
to inform you that we've, um,
我们找到您丢失的货物了
we've located your missing cargo.
你们找到我父亲的棺材了
My father's coffin-- you found it?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
今晚就能送回洛杉矶
It'll be arriving in Los Angeles by the end of the day.
那实在太好了  谢谢
That's, uh, that's great news. Thank you.
不客气  先生
Of course, sir.
敝公司非常抱歉让您等了这么久
We at oceanic are very sorry it's taken so long.
再见  先生
Good day, sir.
我只能这么做
This was the best I could do,
而且会有点疼
And it's gonna hurt a bit.
子弹直接穿过身体
The bullet went straight through,
如果不缝合  很容易感染
But if I don't do this, it's gonna get infected.
忍着点
Okay. I'm sorry.
他们生了个女儿
They had a little girl, you know.
名字叫
Her name was...
Ji Yeon
Ji Yeon.
Jin都没见过她
Jin hadn't even met her yet.
Locke害死了他们
Locke did this to them.
我们得杀了他  Jack
We have to kill him, Jack.
我知道
I know.
我们该出发了
We should get going now.
去哪
Go where?
Sayid死前说Desmond在一口井里
Before Sayid died, he said that Desmond was in a well.
如果Locke想让Desmond死  我们就得找到他
If Locke wants Desmond dead, then we're gonna need him.
欢迎回来  Locke老师  真高兴见到您
Welcome back, mr. Locke. It's good to see you.
谢谢  你也是
Thank you. You, too.
你还敢来
Hey! Don't you dare.
他就是撞Locke老师的人
It's him! The guy who hit mr. Locke!
快打电话报警
Somebody call the police right now!
我看到你撞他
I saw what you did.
-我要报警抓你  -别挡着我
- I'm making a citizen's arrest.  - Do not get in my way.
你休想
Don't you--
我不会再让你伤害Locke老师
I will not let you hurt mr. Locke again!
我不是来伤害他的  我是来
I'm not here to hurt him. I am here...
-帮他放手  -你是谁
- To help him let go.  - Who are you?
你想知道我是谁
You wanna know who I am?
你确定这是近路吗
You sure this is a shortcut, huh?
我在这里住了很久  Miles
I lived in these houses a long time, Miles.
我知道该怎么走
I think I can remember how to get there.
我还在你住这30年前就住过呢
Well, I lived in these houses 30 years before you did--
按现在的时间算  就是上周
Otherwise known as last week.
可我完全不知道我们在哪
And I have no idea where the hell we are.
那你跟着我是好事
Guess it's a good thing you're following me.
你能告诉我
You mind if I ask
你有多少炸药吗  Ben
How much explosive you have access to, Ben?
多到能炸毁飞机十次
More than enough to destroy the plane ten times over
让那个怪物没法离岛
And keep it from ever leaving this island.
这么久了  你确定炸药还在吗
Been a long time. You sure it's still there?
那可是C4炸药  Richard  我藏的时候很谨慎
It's c-4, Richard. I put some thought into hiding it.
我猜猜  藏在饼干罐里吗
Let me guess--cookie jar.
别傻了
Don't be ridiculous.
藏在我书架后的密室里
It's in my secret room behind the bookcase.
怎么了
What's wrong?
就是  我在死人周围会有感应
It's just, I, you know, I get wonky around dead stuff.
你有事情想说吗  Miles
Do you have something you wanna share with us, Miles?
我不确定
I-I don't think--
-是什么  -是Alex
- What is it?  - It's Alex.
你女儿
It's your daughter.
你走后  我葬了她
After you left, I buried her.
谢谢你  Richard
Thank you, Richard.
那是什么  密室吗
What's that? A secreter room?
这是别人告诉我能召唤怪物的地方
It's where I was told I could summon the monster.
后来我才知道是怪物在召唤我
That's before I realized that it was the one summoning me.
Richard  你出的主意
Okay. Richard, it's your idea.
你说我们是炸烂飞机  还是完全摧毁
Are we looking to cripple the plane or blow it to hell?
完全摧毁
Blow it to hell.
那就全部都拿上吧
Then we'd better take it all.
不许动
Don't move!
把手举起来
Show me your hands.
冷静  我绝无恶意
Calm down. It's--it's okay.
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
她是我的人
She's with me.
你好  Benjamin
Hello, Benjamin.
我能进来吗
May I come in?
你来这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
把枪放下  Benjamin
Put the gun down, Benjamin.
去码头拿船上的仪器  然后把船弄沉
Go to the dock, take our equitment from the outrigger and then sink it.
-遵命  -她哪也不能去
- You got it.  - She's not going anywhere.
你要是不回答我  我发誓
If you don't answer me, I swear...
杀了我  你也没有生还的机会
You shoot me, and your last chance of survival will be gone.
去吧  他不会动手
Go. He won't do anything.
你们来这干嘛  Richard
What are you doing here, Richard?
我们来拿炸药
We're getting explosives
炸毁另一座岛上的飞机
To destroy the plane on the other island.
-为什么  -与你无关
- Why would you want to do that?  - None of your damned business.
我一上岛就在飞机上装了炸药
I've had that plane rigged with explosives since I got here.
Benjamin  我还是比你有先见之明
As usual, Benjamin, I'm three steps ahead of you.
你怎么回来的  Charles
How did you get back here, Charles?
Jacob让我来的
Jacob invited me.
撒谎  你根本没见过Jacob
That's a lie. You've never even seen Jacob.
我见过  他来找过我
I most certainly have. He visited me,
就在你们毁了我的货船不久
Not long after your people destroyed my freighter.
他说我的方法是错误的
He convinced me of the error of my ways
并告诉我如何才能
And told me everything I need to know
达到目的
For this exact purpose.
什么目的
What purpose?
Charles
Charles?
请说
Yes.
Locke过来了
It's Locke. He's coming.
-他看到你了吗  -应该没有
- Has he seen you?  - No, I don't think so.
我们的船还在码头  我没时间...
Our boat is still there. I didn't have time to--
快跑  尽快跑回来
Run. Get back here as fast as you can.
如果你们不想死  我们得躲起来
If you don't want to die, we need to hide.
可能会有点刺痛  Linus老师
This may sting a bit, mr. Linus.
应该是Linus博士
It's dr. Linus, actually.
我去帮你拿个冰袋
I'll go get you an ice pack.
Linus博士
Dr. Linus?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
我听说停车场里出了点事
I heard there was a--an incident in the parking lot.
是的  我和人打架了
Yes, I got into a fight.
打架  和谁
A fight? With who?
我看到了那个撞伤你的人  Locke先生
I saw the man that ran you down, Mr. Locke.
他回来了  我一接近他  他就
He was back. I approached him, and he just...
攻击了我
attacked me.
然后发生了非常非常离奇的事情
And then the strangest thing happened.
在他打我的时候
While he was beating me,
我感觉自己看到了什么
I think-- I think I saw something.
你干嘛
What are you doing?
我在报警
I'm calling the police.
也许你不该报警
You may not want to do that.
为什么不报警
Well, why wouldn't I want to?
那个人告诉我说  他并不想伤害你
The man told me that he wasn't trying to hurt you.
他说他想让你放手
He told me that he was trying to get you to let go.
洛杉矶警察局
L.A.P.D.
不知为什么  我相信他的话
And for some reason, I believed him.
喂  洛杉矶警察局
Hello? L.A.P.D.
你明白他的意思吗  Locke先生
Do you have any idea what he was talking about, Mr. Locke?
对你而言是不是别有所指
Does that mean something to you?
喂  洛杉矶警察局
Hello? L.A.P.D.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我想见一下警官
I'd like to see a detective, please.
怎么这身打扮  有人死了吗
What's with the getup? Somebody die?
我父亲博物馆的福利
The benefit at my dad's museum?
我一整周都在和你说的音乐会
The concert I've been telling you about all week?
记起来了吗
Ring a bell?
我一直都记着呢
Yeah, it's all I've been thinking about.
如果你想去的话  还是可以跟我一起去的
You can still be my date if you want to.
那个恨透我的红发小妞会去吗
That red-headed chick that hates me gonna be there?
Charlotte  会啊
Charlotte. Yeah.
那算了
Yeah, pass.
Ford警官  这个人有事要跟你说
Detective Ford, this guy's got somethin' to tell ya.
是吗
Yeah?
几天前在华盛顿塔斯廷高中
There was a hit and run a few days ago
有一起撞人逃逸事件
at Washington Tustin high school.
今天早上
And then this morning
该校的一名教师
one of the teachers there was--
被同一犯罪嫌疑人打成了重伤
was beaten badly by the-- by the same suspect.
然后呢
Yeah? And?
我就是犯罪嫌疑人
I'm the suspect.
谢谢你省去了纳税人
Thanks for saving the taxpayers the trouble
为了缉捕你的钱
of hunting you down.
不客气
You're welcome.
下午好
Good afternoon.
今天过得好吗
And how are you doing today?
好极了
Terrific.
知道那口井的具体位置吗
Any idea exactly where this well is?
Sayid说就在我们的营地附近
Sayid said it was close to our camp.
还有差不多一小时
We're about an hour away.
如果Locke想置Desmond于死地
If Locke wanted Desmond dead,
为什么不直接杀了他
why didn't he just kill him?
谁知道呢  也许这是他的原则吧
Who knows? Maybe it's one of his rules.
潜艇里的炸弹
The bomb on the sub.
你说过他不能杀我们
You said he couldn't kill us.
我之前一直都错了
I've been wrong before.
我害死了他们  对不对
I killed them, didn't I?
没有
No.
是他害死了他们
He killed them.
你没事吧
You all right?
嗯  我没事
Yeah. I'm fine.
好
Okay.
把骨灰给我
Give me the ashes.
什么  你是谁
What? Who are you?
Ilana死后你从她身上拿走的骨灰  把它还给我
Give me the ashes you took from Ilana's things after she died.
我知道就在你口袋里
I know they're in your pocket.
为什么
Why?
因为是我的
Because they're mine.
你要它干什么
What do you want 'em for?
你好  Hugo
Hello, Hugo.
老兄
Dude.
我一直在等你出现  你去哪儿了
I've been waiting for you to show up. Where you been?
无关紧要了  我现在不是在这嘛
Doesn't matter. I'm here now.
你看到一个孩子
Did you see a kid
拿着你的骨灰经过这里吗
run by here with your ashes?
我的骨灰就在那堆火里
My ashes are right there in that fire.
当它烧尽时  你就再也见不到我了
When it burns out, you'll never see me again.
什么
Uh, what?
你该把你朋友叫来
You should get your friends.
我们快成功了  Hugo
We're very close to the end, Hugo.
Charles  我们走
Charles, let's go.
没时间了  Linus有一间密室  快来
There's no time. Linus has a hidden room. Come on.
你还在等什么
What are you waiting for?
我不想躲起来
I'm not interested in hiding.
他迟早都会找到我的
He's gonna find me sooner or later anyway.
我宁愿和他来个了断
I'd rather have it over with.
两个计划都不错  但我还是保命要紧
These are both great plans, but I'm gonna go with surviving.
如果你想找我们  我们从林子那边走
If you need us, we'll be running through the jungle.
Miles  等等
Miles, wait.
把你的手提对讲机给我
Give me your walkie-talkies.
干什么
Why?
因为我问你要
Because I asked.
谢谢  以防万一我需要你
Thank you. In case I need you.
他会杀了你的  你很清楚
He's gonna kill you. You know that.
那我想这就是永别了
Then I guess this is good-bye.
在我等待命定的劫数时  你愿意入伙吗
Care to join me outside while I wait for the inevitable?
我去和他谈  我了解这个人
I-I'm gonna talk to him. I know this man.
他就是想要我和他一起
All he wants is for me to join him,
如果我能让他和我一起离开
and if I can get him to leave with me,
也许能给你们赢得一次机会
maybe that'll give the rest of you a chance.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
正是我要找的人
Just the man I was looking for.
嗯  你找到我了
Well, you found me.
来杯柠檬水吗
Can I get you a glass of lemonade?
我需要你
I need you...
帮我铲除一些人  Ben
to kill some people for me, Ben.
为什么我要这么做呢
And why would I do that?
因为一旦我离开了这座小岛
Because once I leave this island,
你便能将它据为己有
you can have it all to yourself.
好吧
All right.
很好
Good.
码头那边的船是谁的
Now...whose outrigger is that down at the dock?
我想是Charles Widmore的
I believe it's Charles Widmore's.
你知道在哪儿能找到他吗
And do you know where I might find him?
他就躲在我的壁橱里
He's hiding in my closet.
Linus博士
Oh, my god. Hey, Dr. Linus.
你好  Alex
Hello, Alex.
出什么事了
Oh, my god. What happened?
我和一个火气很大的人
I found myself confronting someone
发生了点冲突
that had a bit of a temper.
什么
What?
怎么会有人要伤害你呢
Why would someone want to hurt you?
你就像是个超级大好人
You're, like, the--the nicest guy ever.
我想他们把我和另一个人混淆了
I guess they had me confused with somebody else.
你不该开车
Well, you shouldn't be driving.
我妈妈在那边等我呢
My mom's waiting for me over there.
让我们载你回家吧
Let us give you a ride home.
不了  我可不想麻烦你们
Oh, no, I'm not going to be any trouble to you.
Linus博士  求你了
Dr. Linus, please.
你只有一只手了  看起来就像拿破仑
You've got one hand. You look like Napoleon.
说得没错
Excellent point.
妈妈
Hey, mom!
可以把Linus博士送回家吗
Is it okay if we give Dr. Linus a ride home?
当然
Of course.
您为我女儿尽心尽力
After everything you have done for my daughter,
送您回家是理所应当的事情
a ride is the least we can do.
我是Danielle
I'm Danielle.
Benjamin Linus
Benjamin Linus.
妈妈  Linus博士能到我们家吃晚餐吗
Hey, mom, can Dr. Linus come over for dinner?
今晚吃酒闷仔鸡
It's coq au vin night.
真的不用了
Oh, that's really not necessary--
不行  我们坚持
Oh, no, no, we insist,
即使我们得绑架你
even if we have to kidnap you.
这边  请
Here, please.
能拿一下那个盘子吗
Do you mind getting that plate?
Linus博士
Dr. Linus...
谢谢你
Thank you.
能为除了Alex以外的某个人做饭
It's so nice to be able to cook for someone
真是太开心了
Other than Alex.
请您别介意  请问他父亲在哪
If you don't mind my asking, where is her father?
Alex两岁时他就去世了
He died when Alex was 2.
这也许就是她如此依恋您的原因
That's probably why she's so attached to you.
您说什么
Excuse me?
您对她的种种关心
All the interest you've taken in her,
您对她的一切帮助
All the help you've given...
您是一直以来最接近她父亲的人
You're the closest thing to a father she's ever had.
您
Are you...
您还好吧
Are you all right?
我很好  肯定是洋葱闹的
I'm fine. I'm sure it's the onions.
我下次会少放点
Oh. I'll put in less next time.
你先请
After you.
Charles和他的一个女助手在这
Charles and his lady friend are in here.
她有枪
She's armed,
但我想这对你不构成威胁
but I'm guessing that's not a problem for you.
在这等着
Wait out here.
你不必目睹这些
You don't need to see this.
我想目睹一下
I want to see this.
抱歉  Charles
Sorry, Charles.
真是惊喜呀
What a pleasant surprise.
能不隔着围栏面对面交流真好呀
How nice to be able to talk without those fences between us.
你是哪位
And who might you be?
Zoe  我叫Zoe  我
Zoe. My name is Zoe. I--
别跟他说话  什么也别说
Don't talk to him. Don't say anything.
你为什么杀她
Why would you do that?
你让她别跟我说话  她必定是无名小卒
You told her not to talk to me. That made her pointless.
现在  Charles  很显然你不怕死
Now, Charles, it's clear you're not afraid to die.
那只有一个办法让你
So there's only one way to motivate you
告诉我我想知道的事情了
To tell me what I want to know.
很快一切都将结束  我将得到我想要的
Soon, this will all be over. I'll get what I want.
我也终将离岛
And I'll finally leave this island.
一旦我出岛了  我要做的第一件事
And when I do, the first thing I'm going to do
就是杀掉你女儿
is kill your daughter.
Penny
Penny.
不管我说不说你都会杀了她
You'll kill her whether I talk to you or not.
不  不会的  我向你保证
No, I won't. I give you my word.
那我就该相信你了吗
And I'm supposed to take your word?
告诉我你为什么回来
You tell me why I came back here,
我就不会伤害你女儿了
And I won't hurt your daughter.
我把Desmond Hume带回到这里
I brought Desmond Hume back here
因为他对电磁有很独特的阻抗能力
because of his unique resistance to electromagnetism.
他是最后的手段
He was a measure of last resort.
什么叫"最后的手段"
What do you mean, "Last resort"?
我不会当着他的面再说别的了
I'm not saying any more in front of him.
那小声告诉我
Well, then whisper to me.
他救不了自己的女儿
He doesn't get to save his daughter.
Ben  你总是给我惊喜
Ben... you never cease to amaze me.
好在我已经知道了我想要的
Fortunately, he had already told me what I needed to know,
所以  没啥损失
So... no harm done.
很好
Good.
你是说了还要杀其他人吧
Did you say there were some other people to kill?
你好  Kate  James
Hello, Kate, James.
Jack
Jack.
-他就站在火堆旁向你们问好  -我听见了
- He's right there by the fire. He says hello--  - I heard him.
什么  你能看见他吗
What, you can see him?
是的  我能看见他
Yeah, I can see him.
Kate  Sawyer  你俩呢
Kate? Sawyer? You, too?
你就是把我们的名字写到墙上那人吗
So you're the one who wrote our names on the wall.
是我
I am.
Sun和Jin Kwon  还有Sayid Jarrah
Sun and Jin Kwon and Sayid Jarrah--
-他们的名字也在墙上吗  -是的
- You wrote their names on the wall?  - Yes.
因为这个他们就得死吗
Is that why they're dead?
我非常抱歉
I'm very sorry.
-你非常抱歉  -Kate
- You're sorry?  - Kate.
我想知道原因
No, I wanna know why.
我想知道Sun和Jin还有Sayid没有白白送命
I wanna know that sun and jin and sayid didn't die for nothing.
过来坐下
Come and sit down.
我来告诉你们他们为何而死
And I'll tell you what they died for.
我会告诉你们我为什么选了他们
I'll tell you why I chose them...
为什么选了你们
And why I chose you.
我会告诉你们  关于保护这个岛
And then I'll tell you everything you need to know
你们需要知道的一切
about protecting this island,
因为等这堆火燃尽的时候
because by the time that fire burns out,
你们之中的一人就得开始这样做了
One of you is gonna have to start doing it.
您有空吗
You got a minute?
Locke先生  当然
Mr. Locke. Yes.
快请进
Yes, come on in.
那是你儿子吗
Is that your son?
是的  那是去年感恩节拍的
Yes. That's, uh, last Thanksgiving.
他长得很像你
He looks just like you.
可别告诉他
Don't tell him that.
请问我能为您做点什么吗  Locke先生
So what can I do for you, mr. Locke?
Shepherd医生  您和我搭乘了悉尼来的同一航班
Dr. Shephard, you and I were on the same plane from Sydney.
您给了我名片
You gave me your card, and...
第二天我就扔了  请别介意
Next day, I threw it away. No offense.
没关系
None taken.
不说这个了
Anyway...
几天之后我被车撞了
Then a few days later, I get hit by a car.
洛杉矶这么多医生
And of all the doctors in Los Angeles,
偏偏我又遇上您
I ended up with you.
您救了我之后  仍想治好我的瘫痪
Then a--after you saved my life, you still wanna fix me,
而我仍然  不希望被治好
and I still... don't wanna be fixed.
就这样
Okay.
但之后
Then...
那个撞倒我的人今天再次来到我学校
The man who ran me down shows up at my school today again.
在停车场把一个老师狠狠打了一顿
He beat up a teacher in the parking lot.
但你知道他对他说了什么吗
But do you know what he said to him?
他说他并不是想伤害我
He said that he wasn't there to hurt me.
他只是想帮我"放手"
He was there to help me "let go",
跟上次咱们见面时
Which is exactly the same thing that you said to me
您对我说的一模一样
the last time you and I saw each other.
不好意思  你的意思是
I'm sorry. Are--are you saying
我派了这个人去撞你
that I sent this man to run you down?
不不不
No. No, no. No, no, no.
但如果这一切
But--but what if all this...
也许是事出有因呢
maybe this is happening for a reason.
也许你本该治好我呢
Maybe you're supposed to fix me.
Locke先生  我是想治好你
Mr. Locke, I want to fix you,
但我想您把巧合误解为命运了
but I think you're mistaking coincidence for fate.
随您怎么说  但现在我来了
You can call it whatever you want, but here I am,
而且我
And I...
我想我已准备好摆脱这个轮椅了
I think I'm ready to get out of this chair.
我不知道该从何说起
I don't really know where to start.
那就说说你为什么带我们来这个岛吧
How about with why you brought us to the island?
我把你们所有人带来是因为我犯了个错误
I brought all of you here because I made a mistake.
很久很久以前犯下的错误
A mistake I made a very long time ago,
而现在就因为它
And now because of that,
很可能你们每个人
there's a very good chance that every single one of you
以及你们在乎的每个人都会因此而死
and every you've ever cared about is going to die.
什么错误
What mistake?
你们所说的"黑烟"
You call him "the monster".
对于他的行为我负有责任
But I'm responsible for what happened to him.
是我害他变成那样
I made him that way.
从那以后
And ever since then,
他一直都在试图杀了我
He's been trying to kill me.
他搞清如何下手只是时间问题
It was only a matter of time before he figured out how,
当他成功了  得有人来接替我
And when he did, someone would have to replace me.
所以我把你们都带来这了
And that's why I brought you all here.
跟我说说  Jacob
Tell me something, Jacob.
为什么我要因为你的错误而受惩罚
Why do I gotta be punished for your mistake?
你凭什么觉得你能插手我的生活
What made you think you can mess with my life?
我活得好好的  你却非把我拉来这破地
I was doin' just fine till you dragged my ass to this damn rock.
不  你活得不好
No, you weren't.
你们谁都活的不好
None of you were.
我并没破坏你们的幸福生活
I didn't pluck any of you out of a happy existence.
你们都不完美
You were all flawed.
选你们是因为你们像我
I chose you because you were like me.
你们都是独一无二的
You were all alone.
你们都在寻觅着什么
You were all looking for something
在那个世界却无法找到
that you couldn't find out there.
我选择你们是因为你们需要这个岛
I chose you because you needed this place
正如我需要你们一样
as much as it needed you.
那为什么从墙上划掉了我的名字
Why did you cross my name off of your wall?
因为你做了母亲
Because you became a mother.
那只是洞里画的一条粉笔道
It's just a line of chalk in a cave.
Kate  如果愿意你也有份儿
The job is yours if you want it, Kate.
要我们做什么
What is the job?
岛中心有处光
There's a light at the center of the island.
你们得确保那光永不熄灭
You have to make sure it never goes out.
你们得守护它
That's how you protect it.
你那"黑烟"朋友说那没什么可保护的
Your monster friend said there was nothing to protect it from.
你们就是要保证别让他靠近
You have to protect it from him.
你们要做到我无法做到
You must do what I couldn't...
-无能为力的  -要我们杀了他
- What I wasn't able to do. - You want us to kill him.
-那可能吗  -但愿吧
- Is that even possible? - I hope so,
因为他肯定会设法杀掉你们
Because he is certainly going to try to kill you.
那么...
So...
你打算怎么选
How you gonna pick?
Hugo  不是我要选
I'm not going to pick, Hugo.
我要让你们拥有我一直都没有的...
I want you to have the one thing that I was never given--
选择
A choice.
要是我们都不选呢
And if none of us chooses it?
那结局会非常凄惨
Then this ends very badly.
我来吧
I'll do it.
这也是我来岛的原因
This is why I'm here.
这是...
This is...
这是我注定要做的
This is what I'm supposed to do.
你确定吗  Jack
Is that a question, Jack?
确定
No.
很好
Good.
那就开始吧
Then it's time.
过去我觉得那家伙有点救世主情结
And I thought that guy had a god complex before.
James  别说了
James.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
很庆幸不是我
I'm just glad it's not me.
还记着你刚到岛上
Do you remember that bamboo field you woke up in
在一片竹林上醒来吗
When you first got here?
记着
Yeah.
穿过竹林再越过山脊
Beyond that field, across a ridge,
就到岛的心脏了
Is the heart of the island.
亮光就在那儿
That's where the light is.
也就是他想办法要去的地方
That's where he's trying to go.
你就是要守护那里
And that's what you have to protect.
穿过竹林吗
Past the bamboo?
可那儿什么也没有
There's nothing out there.
有的  Jack
Yes, there is, Jack.
现在你能找到那儿了
And now you'll be able to get there.
有杯子吗
Do you have a cup?
我真还带着
Yeah. Yeah, actually, I do.
把这喝了
Drink this.
我得保护那里多久
How long am I gonna have to do this job?
尽可能的久
As long as you can.
现在你和我一样了
Now you're like me.
看好了  这就是Jarrah和Hume
All righty. Here's Jarrah and Hume.
隔壁的小丫头是Austen
This little lady next door is Austen.
很高兴把你们都逮住
It's been real nice having y'all...
不过得把你们遣送县监狱
But you're shipping off to county,
好好上路吧
So best of luck and vaya con dios.
你还是能放了我的
You could still let me go.
我干嘛要这么做
Why the hell would I do that?
因为我跟你说过我没罪
Because I told you I was innocent,
你也信了
And you believed me.
没用的
Doesn't matter.
还是没法放你  我是警察
Still can't let you go. I'm a cop.
在我看你可不像个警察
You don't seem like a cop to me.
很高兴认识你
Nice knowing ya.
1-F-21回答
1-F-21 responding.
我觉得是时候跑了
I think it's time to leave.
-什么  -我说咱们现在该跑了
-What? -I said, I think it's time to leave.
准备好逃出去了吗
Are you ready to get out of here?
不好意思你是...
I'm sorry. Who are you?
一个非要自己进来的疯子
He's a crazy person who turned himself in.
你为什么事儿自首的
What'd you turn yourself in for?
我开车撞了个坐轮椅的
I ran over a guy in a wheelchair.
我说对了吧
You see what I mean?
行  就算我是疯子
All right. I'm crazy.
但你们到底要不要跑
But do you want to get out of here or not?
怎么跑  让司机师傅停车吗
So, what, are you just gonna tell the driver to stop?
司机知道在哪儿停  不过等车停了
The driver already knows where to stop. But when that happens,
你们得相信我
you're gonna have to give me your trust.
-信你  -没错儿
- Our trust? - That's right.
因为等我帮你逃走后
Because after I set you free,
我要让你们每人做件事
I'm gonna ask each of you to do something,
你们必须向我保证会去做
And you're gonna have to promise me that you'll do it.
-你怎么说  -没问题  我保证
- So what do you say? - Oh, absolutely, I promise.
你呢
How about you?
一言为定
Okay. Sure.
那好吧
All right, then.
Hume是哪位
Who's Hume?
-是我  -你那拿着要给我的钱的朋友呢
- That's me. - Where's your friend with my money?
不然恐怕我就要
Otherwise, I'm gonna have to say
-把你们几个越狱犯都崩了  -别急  他就来
- I shot all of you trying to escape. - Don't worry. He'll be here.
他来了
Oh, here he comes.
-抱歉我来晚了  哥们儿  -没事
- Sorry I'm late, Dude. - Don't worry about it.
你没告诉我
Oh, hey, you didn't tell me Ana
-Ana Lucia也来啊  -我认识你吗 死胖子
- lucia was gonna be here. - Do I know you, tubby?
不认识  我们没见过
Oh. No. We never met.
这是你的钱
Anyways, here's your money.
十二万五对吧
125 grand, right?
没错
Yeah, that's right.
很高兴不认识你
Nice not knowing you.
-她不和我们走吗  -不  她还没准备好
- She's not coming with us? - No, she's not ready yet.
我把大黄蜂给你开来了
I brought you my camaro.
车钥匙在门毡下面
The keys are under the floor mat.
你要的都在后备箱里  -太好了
- Everything you need's is in the trunk. - All right, good.
知道把他们带到哪儿吧
Um, you know where you're taking 'em, yeah?
-当然  -那好咱走
- Absolutely. - All right, well, we should get going.
好  你跟着他  你跟我走
Okay, you're with him, and you're with me.
我跟你走什么意思
What do you mean, I'm with you?
我们...
We...
我们去听音乐会
Are going to a concert.
走吧
Let's go.
能问你点事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
说
Shoot.
要是你随时都能变成黑烟
If you can turn yourself into smoke whenever you want,
那干嘛还费劲走路
Why do you bother walking?
我喜欢脚走在地面上那种感觉
I like the feel of my feet on the ground.
这样我觉着自己还是人类
Reminds me that I was human.
咱到了
We're here.
口渴了吗
Are you thirsty?
这就是我把Desmond Hume推下去的那口井
This is the well I threw Desmond Hume into.
怎么回事
What's the matter?
我派Sayid去干掉Desmond
I sent Sayid to kill Desmond.
显然他没杀
Obviously, he didn't.
看来有人帮他逃出去了
Looks like someone helped him out.
不  Ben  是有人帮了我一把
No, Ben. Someone helped me out.
Widmore和你说什么了
What did Widmore say to you?
他说有Desmond就万无一失了
He said Desmond was a fail-safe.
就像Jacob手上一个杀手锏
Jacob's last resort in case, god forbid,
我曾想方设法把他那些候选人都杀了
I managed to kill all of his beloved candidates--
他阻止我离开的最后办法
One final way to make sure that I never leave this place.
那他活着你怎么还高兴呢
Then... why are you happy that he's still alive?
因为我要找到Desmond
Because I'm gonna find Desmond.
一旦找到了他  他就会帮我
And when I do, he's gonna help me
做那件我永远无法做到的事
do the one thing that I could never do myself.
我要毁掉这个岛
I'm gonna destroy the island.